That's Thursday, November 17th, at the hotel.
那是星期四, 11月17日, 在酒店.
All day?
一整天?
Yes. We start at 8:30 in the morning.
是的. 咱们开始于8:30  在早上
With coffee.
与咖啡(一起).
Yes. Coffee starts at 8:30 and ends at 9.
是的. 咖啡开始于8:30, 结束于9点.
... eight-thirty to nine.
... 8点半到9点.
The opening address begins at 9 o'clock sharp.
开幕辞开始于9点 整.
Workshops run from 9：30 to noon.
研讨会从9:30到正午.
Then lunch.
然后午餐.
One hour?
1小时?
Yes.
对的
The second session goes from one to about 4:15.
第二场从1点到大约4:15.
Discussion ends at 4:45.
讨论结束于4:45.
Then a small reception.
然后一个小招待会.
Until what time?
直到什么时间?
Oh...  Sorry.
Oh... 对不起
That's my watch alarm.
那是我的手表闹钟.
I have an appointment back at the hotel at eleven o'clock.
我有个预约 在酒店 在11点钟时
Is it eleven already?
11点了  已经?
No, no. Actually, it's 10:30.
没, 没. 事实呢, 是10:30.
I set my watch half an hour fast.
我把我的表调快了半个小时.
You're never late, are you?
你永远不迟到, 是吗?
Never. I can't be!
永不. 我不能(迟到)!